Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Oh...
♪ 哦...
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he. ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense be
something you wish... ♪
♪ 如果航海方面的废话是
你想要的东西...♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish. ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Ready?
SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 准备好了吗？
海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Wait for it...
等等吧...
Another day, another migraine.
另一天，又是偏头痛。
Mi...
米...
graine.
颗粒。
Isn't it great
不是很好吗
working at
the Krusty Krab,
Squidward?
工作于
蟹堡王，
章鱼哥？
Huh? Isn't it?
啊？不是吗？
Working here?
在这里工作？
Yeah, great.
是的，太棒了。
Yeah.Yeah.
是啊是啊。
Oh, yeah. Yes!
哦，是的。是的！
Hold that thought, Squidward.
保持这个想法，章鱼哥。
I'm due in the parking lot
for early morning litter patrol.
我该到停车场了
清晨进行垃圾巡逻。
May Neptune shine brightly
on my harvest.
愿海王星闪耀
论我的收获。
Litter.
垃圾。
Looks like someone
missed the trash basket,
看起来像某人
错过了垃圾桶，
huh, Mr. Candy Wrapper?
嗯，糖果包装先生？
Kids these days.
这年头的孩子们。
I've never seen
such an epidemic!
我从未见过
如此流行病！
Well, at least
it's all over now.
嗯，至少
现在一切都结束了。
Huh?
啊？
Huh?!
啊？！
Huh?
啊？
Where is all this litter
coming from?
这些垃圾在哪里
来自？
Not on my watch.
不在我的监视之下。
Sir, I will have you know
先生，我会让你知道
it's against the law to litter.
乱扔垃圾是违法的。
Ha! What are you
going to do,
哈!你会怎样做，
call the police?
打电话叫警察？
Yes.
是的。
How's it going, lieutenant?
怎么样，中尉？
Well, let's just say
I hope our litterbug there
好吧，我们就说一下
我希望我们的垃圾虫在那里
saved room
for his just desserts.
保存的房间
为了他的甜点。
Yeah!
是的！
Just desserts.
只是甜点。
Whatever.
任何。
SpongeBob,
don't you know
who that is?
海绵宝宝，
你不知道吗
那是谁？
Who?
WHO？
世界卫生组织？
That's the Tattletale Strangler!
这就是流言蜚语扼杀者！
Who?
WHO？
世界卫生组织？
The Tattletale Strangler!
流言蜚语扼杀者！
He's promised to strangle anyone
他发誓要勒死任何人
who turns him in!
谁把他举报了！
He seems kind of angry with us,
eh, Squidward?
他似乎对我们有点生气
呃，章鱼哥？
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
You're going
to do time,
Strangler.
你要去
做时间，
绞杀者。
Hard time.
艰难的时光。
Hi, officers.
嗨，军官们。
So he's going to jail, right?
所以他要进监狱了，对吗？
Who, Strangler?
谁，扼杀者？
Yeah, Strangler.
是的，绞杀者。
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
He's going to jail
for a long time.
他要进监狱了
很长一段时间。
Hey, that looks like me!
嘿，这看起来像我！
Don't worry, SpongeBob,
别担心，海绵宝宝，
he won't be able
to strangle you.
他不能
勒死你。
Yeah, we got him
chained up
real good.
是的，我们抓住了他
拴起来
真的很好。
He'll never get away.
他永远不会逃脱。
Oops, not again.
哎呀，又不行了。
Yup, he got away.
是的，他逃走了。
You nice officers
will protect me, right?
你们这些好军官
会保护我的，对吗？
We ain't bodyguards, kid.
我们不是保镖，孩子。
Yeah, give us a call
是的，给我们打电话
if you see him
again, tattletale.
如果你看到他
又是，流言蜚语。
Those officers are right...
I need a bodyguard.
那些官员说得对……
我需要一名保镖。
Mr. Krabs!
蟹老板！
There's a maniac after me.
有一个疯子在追我。
I need a bodyguard!
我需要一个保镖！
I wasn't five-time
golden claws in the navy
我没有五次
海军中的金色爪子
for nothing.
无缘无故。
When he see me moves,
当他看到我的动作时
he'll be running scared.
他会害怕地逃跑。
So where is this little bully,
那么这个小恶霸在哪里呢？
down at the park?
在公园下面？
The soda shop?
汽水店？
What does he look like, eh, boy?
他看起来像什么，呃，男孩？
This would be him,
Mr. Krabs.
这将是他，
蟹老板。
The Tattletale Strangler!
流言蜚语扼杀者！
Go away, SpongeBob.
走开，海绵宝宝。
Take your death cloud with you!
带上你的死亡云吧！
Hold me!
抱紧我！
That's it,
I got to get out of town
就是这样，
我必须出城
till I can find a bodyguard.
直到我能找到保镖。
Bodyguard, huh?
保镖吧？
Uh, I might be able
to help you out.
呃，我也许可以
来帮助你。
You don't understand, mister.
你不明白，先生。
I need protection from
the scariest guy in town.
我需要保护
镇上最可怕的人。
Here's his picture.
这是他的照片。
He doesn't look so tough.
他看上去并不那么坚强。
I tattled on him,
我闲聊他，
and now he wants to strangle me
现在他想勒死我
with his diabolical hands!
用他那双邪恶的手！
I hope they're not dirty.
我希望它们不脏。
Huh?
啊？
Uh-oh, there's too many
witnesses around here.
呃哦，太多了
周围的目击者。
Listen, kid, I could
be your bodyguard.
听着，孩子，我可以
做你的保镖。
Here's my card.
这是我的名片。
Hmm...
唔...
Looks good to me.
我觉得不错。
You're hired!
你被录用了！
I feel safer already.
What's next?
我已经感觉更安全了。
接下来怎么办？
Well, the maniac
could be anywhere
嗯，疯子
可能在任何地方
wearing a disguise.
穿着伪装。
He could be that old man.
他可能就是那个老人。
Or that baby.
或者那个婴儿。
Or that pebble!
或者那块鹅卵石！
Or that stick.
或者那根棍子。
Or that receipt
或者那张收据
for the Phony Baloney
Mustache Emporium.
为了虚伪的胡言乱语
小胡子商场。
Huh? Uh,
that's mine.
啊？呃，
那是我的。
Oh, bodyguard, my body is
in your guarding hands.
噢，保镖，我的身体是
在你守护的手中。
What do we do first?
我们首先做什么？
Uh... I suggest
we go to a nice quiet,
secluded location,
呃……我建议
我们去一个美好的安静的地方，
位置僻静，
like behind
an old dumpster,
or a dark alley.
就像在后面
一个旧垃圾箱，
或黑暗的小巷。
We could go to my house
我们可以去我家
and turn off all the lights.
并关掉所有的灯。
Perfect.
完美的。
That way no one
could hear you
being strangled...
这样就没有人了
能听到你的声音
被勒死……
I mean, uh, uh, protected.
我的意思是，呃，呃，受到保护。
Perfect.
完美的。
Yes, excellent.
是的，非常好。
Ah, but first
I got to do a few errands.
啊，但是首先
我得做几件事。
Uh, okay, but let's
make it quick.
呃，好吧，但是让我们
快点。
"Quick" is my middle name.
“快”是我的中间名。
Let's see, paper towels.
让我们看看，纸巾。
This one says,
"Best paper towel around."
这位说，
“最好的纸巾。”
This one says,
"Best paper towel in town."
这位说，
“镇上最好的纸巾。”
Hmm.
唔。
"In town."
“在城里。”
"Around."
“大约。”
"In town."
“在城里。”
"Around."
“大约。”
What do you think, bodyguard?
保镖你觉得怎么样？
Whatever gets us
to your house quicker.
无论什么让我们
更快到你家。
I'll take both!
我两个都要！
Here you go,
Mr. SquarePants.
给你，
方裤先生。
Hmm...
唔...
Is there something wrong?
有什么问题吗？
I'm not sure if
these are my pants.
我不确定是否
这是我的裤子。
How about this one, bodyguard?
保镖，这个怎么样？
Too overbearing?
太霸道了？
Can we just go to your house?
我们可以去你家吗？
Here we are, SquarePants Manor.
我们到了，方裤庄园。
Bodyguard, let me just
take this opportunity
保镖，让我
借此机会
to say you're the best bodyguard
a fellow could hope to have.
说你是最好的保镖
一个人可能希望拥有。
All right, enough
of the sappy talk.
好吧，够了
多愁善感的谈话。
Open the door
so I can strangle you...
打开门
这样我就可以掐死你了...
I mean, uh, choke you...
我的意思是，呃，窒息你...
I mean, uh, crush
your windpipe... I mean...
我的意思是，呃，迷恋
你的气管...我是说...
"Protect me"?
“保护我”？
Thanks.
谢谢。
Don't mention it, Strangler...
别提了，绞杀者……
I mean "bodyguard."
我的意思是“保镖”。
Now, where did I put my key?
现在，我把钥匙放在哪里了？
Well, I can't find them.
嗯，我找不到他们。
Do you want to take a look?
你想看一下吗？
Forget the key!
忘记带钥匙了！
Let's climb through this window.
让我们爬进这扇窗户吧。
I can't reach it.
我够不着。
Can you hop up
on my shoulders, kid?
你能跳起来吗
在我的肩膀上吗，孩子？
Sure.
当然。
With these spiky cleats,
anything is possible.
有了这些尖刺的防滑鞋，
一切皆有可能。
"Cleats"?
“夹板”？
Get your feet
out of my eye sockets!
站起来
从我的眼窝里出来！
I'm trying, but my cleats
are stuck in your corneas!
我正在努力，但我的鞋
卡在你的角膜里了！
Get off! Get off!
下车！下车！
Oh, oh, oh!
哦，哦，哦！
Don't be mad, bodyguard.
别生气，保镖。
Let me just grab the key
I keep under the mat
让我抓住钥匙
我放在垫子下面
and we can get inside.
我们可以进去了。
There you are,
you little rascal.
你在那里，
你这个小流氓。
Now to put it in the lock,
现在把它放进锁里，
which should activate
the tumblers,
哪个应该激活
玻璃杯，
thus opening the door.
从而打开门。
Step inside...
走进去...
Close the door...
关门...
Well, here we are.
好吧，我们到了。
I finally got you all alone!
我终于独自一人了！
I know, isn't it great?
我知道，这不是很好吗？
Ooh!
哦！
Now you're going to
get yours, tattletale!
现在你要
得到你的，流言蜚语！
Surprise!
惊喜！
A surprise party to celebrate
惊喜派对庆祝
my perfect on-time
percentage at work?
我的完美准时
工作百分比？
Oh, how'd you guys know?
哦，你们怎么知道的？
It's on the invitations
you sent us.
邀请函上有
你派我们来的。
Let's boogie!
让我们布吉吧！
Bye, everybody,
thanks for coming!
再见，大家，
感谢您的光临！
Bye, Mr. Krabs, bye, Plankton,
bye, Sandy, bye, Larry,
再见，蟹老板，再见，浮游生物，
再见，桑迪，再见，拉里，
bye, Pearl, bye, Mrs. Puff, bye,
Squidward, bye, the rest.
再见，珀尔，再见，普芙夫人，再见，
章鱼哥，再见，剩下的。
Alone at last.
终于孤身一人了
Huh? What? What?
啊？什么？什么？
So we're all alone now?
所以我们现在都是孤独一人了？
Just you, me
and the floorboards.
只有你、我
和地板。
Yeah!
是的！
Happy birthday, SpongeBob!
生日快乐，海绵宝宝！
How did you guys know
today is my birthday?
你们怎么知道的
今天是我的生日吗？
We just do what
the invitations say.
我们只是做些什么
邀请函上说。
Let's boogie some more!
让我们再来点布吉吧！
Thanks for coming!
感谢您的光临！
Whew!
哇！
Alone again.
又孤身一人了。
Is it true?
这是真的吗？
Everybody's gone?
大家都走了吗？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
No more parties today?
今天不再聚会了吗？
You've got everything
you need now?
你已经拥有了一切
你现在需要吗？
Nobody's left,
we're completely alone?
一个人都没有留下
我们完全孤独吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
In that case...
在这种情况下...
Great parties, huh?
很棒的派对，是吧？
Oh!
哦！
Sorry, tubby, you got to go.
抱歉，胖子，你得走了。
Wait, we can trust Patrick.
等等，我们可以相信帕特里克。
He's my best friend.
他是我最好的朋友。
Well, uh, I can't
take any chances.
嗯，呃，我不能
抓住一切机会。
For all we know, uh,
he could be the Strangler.
据我们所知，呃，
他可能是绞杀者。
I'm the Strangler?!
我就是绞杀者？！
Oh, I should have known!
哦，我早该知道的！
I got to turn myself in!
我得去自首！
So Patrick's the Strangler.
所以帕特里克是绞杀者。
Gee, you think you know a guy.
哎呀，你以为你认识一个人。
He's not the Strangler!
他不是绞杀者！
He's not?
他不是吗？
I am!
我是！
Hey, how'd you do that
without shaving cream?
嘿，你是怎么做到的
没有剃须膏？
Oh, it's a fake, you idiot!
噢，这是假的，你这个白痴！
I bought it at the party store!
我是在派对商店买的！
Did someone say "party"?
有人说“聚会”吗？
I can't take it!
我受不了！
Wait, bodyguard,
I need protection!
等等，保镖，
我需要保护！
Step on it!
踩它！
I'm being chased by a maniac!
我正在被一个疯子追赶！
I'm not safe!
我不安全！
Come back!
回来！
Finally! Away from that guy.
最后！远离那个人。
Good idea, bodyguard.
好主意，保镖。
He'll never find us up here.
他永远不会在这里找到我们。
Good thinking, bodyguard.
好主意，保镖。
The Strangler could have been
on that plane.
绞杀者可能是
在那架飞机上。
Bodyguard!
保镖！
Look, kid...
瞧，孩子……
I'm not your bodyguard!
我不是你的保镖！
I'm the Strangler.
我是绞杀者。
See?
看？
The Strangler!
绞杀者！
Good work, SpongeBob.
干得好，海绵宝宝。
You put the Strangler
behind bars.
你把绞杀者
关在监狱里。
At least I'm safe
from that yellow idiot.
至少我是安全的
来自那个黄色白痴。
Hey, Mack.
嘿，马克。
What are you in for?
你进来干什么？
Well, Patrick, here it is,
the Palace of Pranks,
好吧，帕特里克，就是这里，
恶作剧宫殿，
the greatest novelty shop
in Bikini Bottom.
最伟大的新奇店
在比基尼底部。
All the greatest pranksters
shop here.
所有最伟大的恶作剧者
在这里购物。
This is where I got
my gag seanut brittle can.
这就是我得到的地方
我的堵嘴花生脆罐头。
Oh, boy, seanut brittle...
Give me!
哦，孩子，花生脆……
给我！
Patrick, wait, it's
a booby trap, remember?
帕特里克，等等，这是
一个诱杀装置，还记得吗？
Nice try, SquarePants, but it's
not going to work this time.
不错的尝试，SquarePants，但它是
这次不去上班了。
I'm going to have some of
your delicious seanut brittle.
我要一些
你美味的花生脆。
Where's the seanut brittle?
哪里有花生脆？
That gets funnier every time
you say it, Patrick.
每次都变得更有趣
你说吧，帕特里克。
Come on, let's go inside.
来吧，我们进去吧。
Seanut brittle.
花生脆。
Ah!
啊!
Nothing compares to the smell
of cheap plastic novelty items.
没有什么能与气味相比
廉价的塑料新奇物品。
Pranks, gags and gross-out toys
as far as the eye can see.
恶作剧、恶作剧和恶心的玩具
一眼望去。
Isn't it everything I said
it would be, Patrick?
这不是我说的一切吗
会是这样吗，帕特里克？
Hey, seanut brittle!
嘿，花生脆！
Oh, darn it, not again.
哦，该死，不要再这样了。
Good to see you, SpongeBob.
很高兴见到你，海绵宝宝。
How's my number one
customer doing?
我的第一怎么样
客户在做什么？
Great, Frank.
太棒了，弗兰克。
This is my friend, Patrick.
这是我的朋友帕特里克。
He wants to become
a prankster, too.
他想成为
也是个恶作剧者。
Well, pleasure
to meet you, Patrick.
嗯，很高兴
见到你，帕特里克。
That's your first lesson, son...
这是你的第一堂课，儿子……
The granddaddy of all pranks,
所有恶作剧的祖父，
the joy buzzer.
欢乐蜂鸣器。
I don't get it.
我不明白。
You don't have to get it.
你不必得到它。
The prank is
for the enjoyment
of the prankster.
恶作剧是
为了享受
恶作剧者的。
You see, Patrick,
Frank here is the master.
你看，帕特里克，
弗兰克是这里的主人。
I learned all I know
about pranks from him.
我学会了我所知道的一切
关于他的恶作剧。
Frank, let's see
what you've got.
弗兰克，让我们看看
你有什么。
Well, this came in
just this morning.
嗯，这个进来了
就在今天早上。
Have some gum.
吃点口香糖吧
Ha! Exploding chewing gum,
only $9.95.
哈!口香糖爆炸，
只需 9.95 美元。
I don't get it.
我不明白。
What can we get for one dollar?
一美元我们能得到什么？
One dollar will get you
this fake gag dollar...
一美元就能给你
这个假的恶作剧美元...
Fool your friends into thinking
you've got a real dollar.
欺骗你的朋友思考
你有一块真正的美元。
What else have you got?
你还有什么？
A whoopee cushion?
欢呼垫？
Nah.
不。
Fake vomit.
假呕吐。
No.
不。
Real vomit.
真想吐。
Eww!
哇！
Have anything good?
有什么好东西吗？
Well, there is one prank
that I've been saving
嗯，有一个恶作剧
我一直在保存的
for a real top-of-the-line
prankster...
真正的顶级
恶作剧者...
Invisible spray.
隐形喷雾。
Wow, invisible spray!
哇，隐形喷雾！
But I can see it.
但我能看到它。
Gee, Patrick, just
think of the pranks
哎呀，帕特里克，只是
想想恶作剧
we could pull with this.
我们可以这样做。
Good choice.
不错的选择。
Now, be careful
with that stuff, boys.
现在，要小心
孩子们，用那些东西。
It stains clothes.
它会弄脏衣服。
Thanks, Frank.
谢谢，弗兰克。
Here it is, Patrick,
在这里，帕特里克，
the ultimate prank...
最终的恶作剧...
Invisible spray.
隐形喷雾。
What are we going to do with it?
我们要用它做什么？
I know!
我知道！
We'll go spray the park bench
我们去公园长椅上喷洒
and then sit on it,
然后坐在上面，
and when people walk by,
当人们走过时，
we'll be floating in midair.
我们将漂浮在半空中。
They're floating in midair!
他们漂浮在半空中！
How do they do that?
他们是怎么做到的？
That's the ultimate prank!
这就是终极恶作剧！
Good idea, SpongeBob!
好主意，海绵宝宝！
Well, let's get started.
好吧，让我们开始吧。
Okay, I'm ready.
好的，我准备好了。
Any particular reason
you took your pants off?
任何特定原因
你把裤子脱了吗？
Well, that stuff
stains clothes, right?
嗯，那个东西
衣服上有污渍，对吗？
That it does, Patrick,
that it does.
确实如此，帕特里克，
确实如此。
Good thinking.
好想法。
Here, hold this a second.
在这里，等一下。
Okay, Patrick, give me the can.
好吧，帕特里克，把罐子给我。
I think since spraying
the park bench was my idea,
我想自从喷了之后
公园长椅是我的主意
I should get to spray it.
我应该去喷它。
Patrick, spraying the park bench
帕特里克在公园长椅上喷洒
was myidea.
是我的主意。
Yeah, but I said
it was a good idea.
是的，但我说过
这是个好主意。
Give me that thing.
把那个东西给我。
Hey, the invisible spray works!
嘿，隐形喷雾起作用了！
And on your right if you look,
如果你看的话，在你的右边，
you'll see two
naked guys fighting
over a can of paint.
你会看到两个
裸体男人打架
超过一罐油漆。
Oh, my gosh, Patrick,
help me find our clothes!
哦，天哪，帕特里克，
帮我找到我们的衣服！
I got to handit
to you, SpongeBob.
我必须交出
给你，海绵宝宝。
You look kind of funny.
你看起来有点滑稽。
Righty, where are you?
右，你在哪里？
No one messes with Righty!
没人敢惹Righty！
We'll see how youlike it.
我们会看看你是否喜欢它。
Kind of gives you
an emptyfeeling, huh?
有点给你
一种空虚的感觉吧？
Yeah!
是的！
I seewhat you mean.
我明白你的意思了。
No guts, no glory!
没有勇气，就没有荣耀！
I think this thing is empty.
我觉得这个东西是空的。
Oh, no, it can't be!
噢，不，不可能！
How are we going to pull
off the ultimate prank?
我们要如何拉
结束了终极恶作剧？
Thanks a lot, Patrick.
非常感谢，帕特里克。
You used the last of it.
你用了最后一个。
Hey, I think I found our pants.
嘿，我想我找到了我们的裤子。
Oops!
Here, these are yours.
哎呀！
在这里，这些是你的。
Oh, forget the pants, Patrick.
哦，忘了裤子吧，帕特里克。
Let's get home and
wash this paint off.
我们回家吧
把这油漆洗掉。
Hey, SpongeBob, do you
know what time it is?
嘿，海绵宝宝，你呢
知道现在几点了吗？
Oh, sure, it's...
half past invisible.
哦，当然，这是...
半点看不见。
Gee, it's getting late.
哎呀，已经晚了。
Let's ask this guy.
我们去问问这个人吧。
Sir, but do you have the time?
先生，但是您有时间吗？
Sure, it's ten
to 3:00.
当然可以，十点了
至 3:00。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Don't mention it.
别提了。
Don't mention what?
不提什么？
Who said that?
谁说的？
Me.
我。
Ghosts!
鬼魂！
Hey, I'm no ghost!
嘿嘿，我不是鬼！
The nerve of that guy
and his driving eyeballs.
那家伙的神经
和他那锐利的眼球。
Wait a second, Patrick,
等一下，帕特里克，
my brain just hatched an idea.
我的大脑刚刚萌生了一个想法。
Lay it on me.
放在我身上。
Okay, we're invisible, right?
好吧，我们是隐形的，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
If that guy thought
we were ghosts,
如果那家伙以为
我们曾是幽灵，
we could haunt everybody
in Bikini Bottom.
我们可以困扰每个人
在比基尼底部。
Oh, it's the ultimate prank.
哦，这真是终极恶作剧。
High five!
高五！
Let's go scare us some suckers.
我们去吓吓我们这些傻瓜吧。
Huh?
啊？
That's funny,
I thought I heard voices.
这很有趣，
我以为我听到了声音。
Huh?
啊？
I thought I left that glass
of peanut juice on the table.
我以为我留下了那个玻璃杯
桌上的花生汁。
And didn't I toss
that old lamp out yesterday?
而且我没有折腾吗
昨天那个旧灯灭了吗？
And since when did I acquire
all these portraits of Patrick?
从什么时候开始我获得了
所有这些帕特里克的肖像？
We're ghosts.
我们是鬼魂。
I knew it was you guys!
我就知道是你们！
All right, joke's over.
好了，笑话结束了。
Take off the sheets.
取下床单。
It isghosts!
是鬼！
Boy, we really scared her!
男孩，我们真的吓到她了！
Who's going to be
our next victim?
谁会成为
我们的下一个受害者？
A better question
would be, "Who isn't?"
一个更好的问题
会是，“谁不是？”
Double-dark deep-sea
light diet cake!
双暗深海
轻食减肥蛋糕！
You will soon be mine.
你很快就会成为我的。
Ghosts!
鬼魂！
Huh?
啊？
Ghosts!
鬼魂！
PATRICK AND SPONGEBOB Cowabunga!
帕特里克和海绵宝宝 Cowabunga！
Ghosts!
鬼魂！
Toast.
吐司。
Ghosts!
鬼魂！
It's official... we're the
greatest pranksters ever.
这是官方的...我们是
有史以来最伟大的恶作剧者。
The whole town
thinks we're ghosts.
整个城镇
认为我们是鬼魂。
Yeah.
是的。
There's only one guy
left to scare,
只有一个人
留下来吓唬，
and we'll have pranked everybody
in Bikini Bottom...
我们会恶作剧所有人
在比基尼底部...
Mr. Krabs.
蟹老板。
It says he isn't
scared of ghosts.
据说他不是
害怕鬼。
We'll see about that!
我们拭目以待吧！
Ghosts!
鬼魂！
Hah!
哈！
I ain't afraid of no ghosts!
我什么鬼都不怕！
Every sailor knows a ghost
won't come near a fella
每个水手都认识一个鬼魂
不会靠近一个人
as long as he's wearing
his spotted neckerchief...
只要他穿着
他的斑点领巾……
and his dried-up sea leprechaun.
还有他干涸的海妖精。
And a bit of gold never hurt.
一点金子永远不会有坏处。
But to be on the safe side,
但为了安全起见，
I'm also wearing me pants
in a melvin knot,
我也穿我的裤子
在梅尔文结中，
got me shivering timber brace,
让我颤抖的木支架，
and the hairs on the back
of me neck are taped down.
和后面的毛发
我的脖子被胶带粘住了。
And I'm all wrapped up
in a suit of anti-ghost armor.
我全身心投入
身穿反鬼铠甲。
And if none of this stuff works,
I've got me secret weapon...
如果这些东西都不起作用
我有秘密武器...
The specter deflector.
幽灵偏转器。
So just try and get me,
you ghosts!
所以试着让我，
你们这些鬼魂！
Bring it on!
来吧！
Krabs.
螃蟹。
Krabs, we've come to haunt you.
蟹蟹们，我们是来骚扰你们的。
Stay back, I'm well-armed!
退后一步，我全副武装！
I'm warning you.
我警告你。
Ooh!
哦！
Boo.
嘘。
I got to get out of here!
我必须离开这里！
You can't escape, Krabs.
你逃不掉的，蟹蟹。
We glued the door shut.
我们把门粘上了。
You'll never get me!
你永远得不到我！
Nice try, Krabs, but we replaced
all the glass with rubber.
不错的尝试，螃蟹，但我们更换了
所有玻璃都带有橡胶。
Too late, Krabs, we've already
clogged all the toilets.
太晚了，蟹蟹，我们已经
堵塞了所有的厕所。
Please, spirits, leave me be.
拜托，精灵们，让我安静吧。
We got him good, SpongeBob.
我们把他搞定了，海绵宝宝。
Wait, Patrick,
I've got one more idea.
等等，帕特里克，
我还有一个想法。
You're going to pay, Krabs.
你要付钱的，蟹蟹。
No, spirits, please!
不，请精神！
No!
不！
Don't burn me dollar!
别烧我美元！
Well, well, well, if it isn't
SpongeBob and Patrick.
好吧好吧，如果不是的话
海绵宝宝和帕特里克。
I know not these names
我不知道这些名字
of which you speak.
你所说的。
Uh, SpongeBob.
呃，海绵宝宝。
SpongeBob, we're visible again.
海绵宝宝，我们又出现了。
So you two are
the Bikini Bottom ghosts.
所以你们两个是
比基尼泳裤鬼魂。
We're really sorry,
Mr. Krabs.
我们真的很抱歉，
蟹老板。
Please don't chop us
up into little pieces
and eat them.
请不要砍我们
分成小块
并吃掉它们。
Hey, come on, boys, I'm hip.
嘿，来吧，孩子们，我很时髦。
I pulled my share of pranks
when I was your age,
我做了我的恶作剧
当我在你这个年纪的时候
had me some laughs.
让我笑了。
That's what we did tonight,
right?
这就是我们今晚所做的
对吗？
We had a good laugh.
我们笑得很开心。
Come on, laugh with me.
来吧，和我一起笑吧。
Uh, any particular reason
you boys are naked?
呃，有什么特殊原因吗
你们男孩是裸体的吗？
Yeah, the invisible
paint stains clothes.
是的，看不见的
油漆弄脏衣服。
Of course it does.
当然可以。
Well, you two better hurry home
before someone sees you nude.
好吧，你们两个还是赶紧回家吧
在有人看到你的裸体之前。
Yeah, I think I'd
die of embarrassment
if that happened.
是的，我想我会
尴尬而死
如果发生这种情况。
Me, too.
我也是。
No, wouldn't want that,
would we?
不，不想这样，
我们会吗？
It's getting late now.
现在已经很晚了。
You pranksters better get going.
你们这些恶作剧者最好赶紧行动起来。
Mr. Krabs, thanks for
being such a good sport.
蟹老板，谢谢你
这是一项如此好的运动。
Don't mention it.
别提了。
That Mr. Krabs, always
looking out for me.
那个蟹老板，总是
照顾我。
What a guy!
真是个家伙啊！
Yeah.
是的。
The Krusty Krab presents...
蟹堡王呈现...
live nude pranksters!
现场裸体恶作剧者！
Starring the Bikini Bottom
ghosts.
主演比基尼泳裤
鬼魂。
Patrick!
帕特里克！
Yeah?
是的？
We should have bought
the whoopee cushion.
我们应该买
欢呼垫。
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org